<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robins Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Robins Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 01:37:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running a Large Language Model on my School Supercomputer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hpc_llm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 01:37:53 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hpc_llm/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! I was having some fun browsing /r/localLLaMA and I saw that llama3 popped up!&#xA;At the time it was real good for its parameter size and just in general, so I wanted to try to run it!&#xA;Of course, I could&amp;rsquo;ve ran it in a Q5 quantized form on my desktop with a 1080ti, however, I felt like using my school funding to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hardest Class I took was in Middle School</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hardest_class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hardest_class/</guid>
      <description>Right now, I’m a 4th year computer science and engineering student at SCU.&#xA;I’ve taken many foundational and theoretical/technical courses that had a good amount of difficulty to them. Out of all my courses at SCU, these were probably the most challenging:&#xA;Machine Learning + Data Mining – COEN140 – David Anastasiu Compilers – Coen175 – Darren Atkinson Digital Logic Design – ELEN 160 – Mamudur Rahman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LupinStory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lupinstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 11:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lupinstory/</guid>
      <description>LupinStory I tried to recreate a funny little Maplestory game that I played as a little kid.&#xA;It was called MonkeyStory.&#xA;Maplestory was a big part of my childhood, I played a ton of it with my brother and I remember revolving a lot a lot of time around it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCU Things</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/scu_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 15:11:41 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/scu_things/</guid>
      <description>Santa Clara University Things I&amp;rsquo;m from the COEN / CSEN, so I can only give you advice from there. social anx, asian&#xA;Use your time at college to explore who you are or want to be. This can be thru a variety of means&#xA;Meet new people Dabble in new activities eat mysterious substances APSU / CSA / KSA:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:50:27 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? In case you wanted to learn more about me I guess this is where you can e-stalk me.&#xA;As you have read in the About Me page, I have an interest in a wide variety of subjects which include math, philosophy, branches of computer science, and literature.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
